

Teixeira

React Developer

Portfolio: dantxal.com

github.com/dantxal

dantxal@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/daniel-txal

About me

Hello, I am Daniel Teixeira, 26-years old, Full Stack developer, I'm very tech-savvy and a React enthusiast.

I started studying React in the first-half of 2019, and have been working and studying it together with NodeJS and React Native.

I like to keep myself updated with new technologies and metodologies in this spectrum.

am proficient in spoken and written English.

Professional Experience

Full Stack Developer Snapboard Inc. • Remote Oct, 2019 - Aug, 2020

Product design, implementing integrations, creating components, e2e testing. Typescript, React, NodeJS, Cypress.io, Passport

React Developer

Freelance

Full Time

Freelancing

Remote

Jun, 2019 - Oct, 2019

Comissioned apps for local businesses. React, Electron

Education

React Tech Stack - Bootcamp

Aug, 2019 - Oct, 2019 Rocketseat

Imersive course on the React, Node and React Native ecosystem. Many practical exercises, developed entire apps with databases, back-end, front-end and mobile.

The course also included:

- DevOps with docker, mongodb, postgres;
- Advanced styling using styled-components library;
- State management with Redux and Redux-Saga;
- Tests with Jest.

Javascript and React Courses

codewithmosh.com Apr, 2019 - May, 2019

Introductory course to Javascript ES6, and React. During the course I developed an entire Video Rental app with a fake API.

English Course

CILBSB **I** Jan, 2007 - Dec, 2011

A 5-years long course with both written and oral tests every semester. The course aims at teaching students everything they might need if they ever decide to study/work in a English-speaking country.